Watch this, it's really cool. Ahem.
(Howard:)Call Leonard Hofstadter.
WOMAN [ON MACHINE]:
Did you say, "Call Helen Boxleitner"?
(Howard:)No. Call Leonard Hofstadter.
Did you say, "Call Temple Beth Seder"?
(Leonard:)- No.
- Here, let me try.
Call M'kflono M'kflooniloo. Ha-ha. Ha.
(Howard's phone:)Calling Rajesh Koothrappali.
[PHONE RINGING]
Oh. It's very impressive.
(Raj:)And a little racist.
If we're through playing
Mock the Flawed Technology...
...can we get on with "Halo" night?
We were supposed to start at 8.
It's now 8:06.
So we'll start now.
(Sheldon:)We have to decide
if those lost six minutes...
...will come out of game time,
bathroom time or the pizza break.
We could split it two, two and two.
(Howard:)If we're having anchovies on the pizza,
we can't take it out of bathroom time.